

Muhammad Awais Ajmal

Senior Unity Game Developer

In my 3 years as a Unity game developer, I've mastered diverse genres, excelled in teamwork, honed my skills in gameplay, UI, performance, and monetization, and learned the importance of timely, high-quality delivery. Ready for more challenges ahead!

awaisajmal02@gmail.com

Bahawalpur, Pakistan

+923039269518

in linkedin.com/in/https://shorturl.at/AHM49

WORK EXPERIENCE

Internship Unity Game Developer JHU Technology

05/2021 - 07/2021

Bahawalpur, Punjab, Pakistan

Junior Unity Game Developer

Nerdo Studio. Inc

07/2021 - 08/2022

Lahore, Punjab, Pakistan

Senior Unity Game Developer

Five River Solution

09/2022 - Present

Islamabad, Pakistan

EDUCATION

Diploma of Associate Engineering(Civil)

TEVTA Punjab

Bahawalpur Pakistan (83.82%)

Bechelor in Computer Science

The Islamia University of Bahawalpur

2016 - 2020

2013 - 2016

Bahawalpur Pakistan (3.71/4)

Master in Computer Science

The Islamia University of Bahawalpur

2020 - 2022

Bahawalpur Pakistan(3.81/4)

SKILLS

PROJECTS

Offroad coach bus simulator

https://rb.gy/qry1q

Forest Wild Werewolf Hunting

• https://rb.gv/y61ea

House Makeover Cleaning

• https://rb.gv/v7hsdu

Scary Grandma Grandpa House 3D

https://shorturl.at/Oi8dB

Angry My Neighbor

• https://rb.gy/6f7e2a

Supermarket Simulator: Shop 3D

https://shorturl.at/gtPKD

Real World T20 Cricket 2024

https://shorturl.at/lNVQj

Car Driving School Games Sim

https://shorturl.at/6BFcB

STRENGTH

Good Communication Skills

Team Player

Time Management

LANGUAGES

Professional Working Proficiency

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

INTERESTS

Research

Play Video Games

Education

Hiking